Finding Aid for the Louis Jolyon West Papers LSC.0590
UCLA Library Special Collections
- 2. Writing., 1950-1998.
  - Letter to the Editor: American Journal of Psychiatry., 1986 April 22-June 25. (Box 14, Folder 10)
    The folder contains correspondence pertaining to letters printed in the journal about psychiatric services to medical students at UCLA. Letter co-signed by Dr. Sherman Mellinkoff.
  - "Drug Testing"., 1990 June-1991 July. (Box 14, Folder 11)
    Possibly submitted to Psychiatric Annals, the Journal of Social Psychiatry.
  - "Bridey Murphy Update"., undated. (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Milton Erickson., 1991 January 31-April 30. (Box 14, Folder 13)
    Ericksonian Therapy
  - "Tarahumara: Revisited"., 1987 April-May 15. (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - "Drug Testing": Contention journal., 1990 May 22-1991 June 10. (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - "Right To Die": Contention journal., 1992 September 11-1993 March 12. (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - "Psychiatry and Scientology": American Psychiatric Association., 1991 August 7-1993 January 22. (Box 14, Folder 17)
    Contains correspondence pertaining to LJW's article not being accepted for publication by the American Psychiatric Association. The article was LJW's Distinguished Psychiatrist Lecturer talk given at the APA Annual Meeting in May 1992.
  - "Diagnosis and Treatment of Pseudo-Identity"., 1994 April 28- June 14. (Box 14, Folder 18)
    Chapter to be part of a book based on the lectures given at the 1994 NPI Grand Rounds.
  - "Pseudo-Identity Syndrome"., 1994 April 5-July 27. (Box 14, Folder 19)
    Folder contains correspondence pertaining to publication of this paper in the Journal of Nervous and Mental Disease.
  - "Child Cult Involvement Decision Tree"., 1984, 1993 June 1-October 27. (Box 14, Folder 20)
    Chapter prepared for Handbook of Child and Adolescent Psychiatry
  - New York Times: Letter to the Editor., 1990 February 18-March 15. (Box 14, Folder 21)
    LJW's letter points out that African American teacher Clara Luper and eight school children requested service at a lunch counter of a large drugstore in Oklahoma City on August 15, 1958, a year and a half before the Greensboro college men did the same at Woolworth's on February 1, 1960.
  - Forward to "Preventing Mental Health Disturbances in Childhood"., 1989 April-June 26. (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - "Ketamine Abuse"., 1994 July 11. (Box 15, Folder 1)
    Prepared for the Journal of Drug Issues, co-authored by James W. Dotson and Deborah L. Ackerman
  - Comment on "Violence and the Violent Patient"., 1986 June 19-September 27. (Box 15, Folder 2)
    Prepared for the American Psychiatric Association Annual Review: Volume 6
  - American College of Psychiatrists., 1973 May 26. (Box 15, Folder 3)
    Folder includes correspondence regarding LJW writing a piece for the American College of Psychiatrists, possibly related to Sector Psychotherapy?
  - Permission to reprint LJW's articles., 1984 September 11-1995 February 3. (Box 15, Folder 4)
    Folder contains correspondence pertaining to requests for permission from LJW to reprint his writings.
  - Requests for copies of LJW's articles., 1987 February 13- 1994 February 3. (Box 15, Folder 5)
    Folder contains phone messages, business cards, post cards, and letters requesting copies of LJW's articles.
  - Requests for copies of LJW's articles-pending., 1986 June 27-1992 January 6. (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Publisher and editors contacts., 1992 May 7- 1986 April 11. (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Requests for contributions., 1987 May 4. (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Writing commitments., 1966 December 29- 1970 October 19. (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Writing commitments., 1969 November 20- 1971 October 8. (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Requests for reprints and correspondence., 1966 May 11- 1971 July 19. (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - "The Future of Psychiatric Education"., 1973 January 18-November 14. (Box 15, Folder 12)
    Folder contains requests for reprints of this paper that was presented at American Psychiatric Association Annual Meeting 1972, and requests for reprints of other articles by LJW. Folder contains note "Original" next to (not attached) to manuscript.
  - "Creativity"., 1966. (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - "The Social Psychiatry of 'Going on Musth' in Elephants"., 1964 June 16-23. (Box 15, Folder 14)
    Noted "MS Pending" for the American Psychopathological Association's 1965 Meeting.
  - "The Season of All Natures"., 1962 November 14. (Box 16, Folder 1)
    Noted "MS Pending" for the journal "The Emotional Factor in Medical Practice."
  - "Psychopathology Produced By Sleep Deprivation"., 1966 December 16-26. (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - "Perceptual Release: A Psychophysiological Theory of Hallucinations"., 1957 October 12-1959 July 28. (Box 16, Folder 3)
    Noted "MS Pending" for the American Journal of Psychiatry. Paper read at APA Annual Meeting in May 1958.
  - "Manic-Depressive Reactions and Delirium"., 1961 April 14-1962 July 17. (Box 16, Folder 4)
    Noted "MS Pending" for journal "Current Therapy."
  - "Textbook of Hypnosis"., 1959 December 11-1962 December 3. (Box 16, Folder 5)
    Noted "Book Pending"
  - "Sleep and Dreams" panel., 1962 May 31-July 16. (Box 16, Folder 6)
    Noted "MS Pending" for the Proceedings of the Third World Congress of Psychiatry
  - "Diagnosis and Treatment of Delirium"., 1962 February 3-July 15. (Box 16, Folder 7)
    Noted "MS Pending" for the Journal of the Oklahoma State Medical Association.
  - Brosin Symposium., undated. (Box 16, Folder 8)
    Noted "Review Pending" for the Journal of Nervous Mental Disease
  - "Six Years of Sit-Ins: Psychodynamic Causes and Effects"., 1964 May 7-1965 October 11. (Box 16, Folder 9)
    Manuscript presented at the APA Annual Meeting, May 7, 1964. Co- authored with Chester M. Pierce, M.D.
  - "The Induction of Abnormal States (Vol. 12)"., 1966 April 1-1967 January 26. (Box 16, Folder 10)
    Paperback series in Abnormal Psychology, McGraw-Hill Co.
  - "Experimental Psychopathology"., 1965 April 21. (Box 16, Folder 11)
    Textbook by N. Garmezy, O.A. Parsons, and LJW.
  - "The Encyclopedia of Mental Health"., 1961 July 6-1962 November 7. (Box 16, Folder 12)
    Correspondence with publisher Franklin Watts, Inc.
  - "Some Participant Observations in Civil Rights Struggles"., 1965. (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - The Psychoanalytic Forum., 1969 March-October. (Box 16, Folder 14)
    Correspondence regarding a discussion of Kurt Schlesinger's "Thoughts on King Lear and the Current Generation Gap."
  - The Journal of Nervous and Mental Disease., 1961 May 18-1966 January 19. (Box 16, Folder 15)
    LJW sat on editorial board
  - American Journal of Psychiatry., 1958 February 3-1959 July 28, 1966 January 5-June 27. (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - "Medicine and Capital Punishment" and "Psychopathology Produced by Sleep Deprivation"., 1965 December 3-4, undated. (Box 16, Folder 17)
    Folder includes the two papers by LJW
  - "Hypnosis"., 1961 October 5-December 1. (Box 16, Folder 18)
    Noted "MS Pending" for the American Journal of Nursing.
  - "New Developments in Mental Health Research"., 1963 February 25-March 22. (Box 16, Folder 19)
    Noted "MS Pending" for journal "Bios". Lecture given at the Oklahoma Academy of Science in February 1963
  - "Hypnosis and the Dissociative Reactions"., 1965 October-1966 August 26. (Box 16, Folder 20)
    Noted "MS Pending" for the Pan American Medical Association's 42nd Anniversary Congress in Buenos Aires, November 26-30, 1967.
  - "The Uses of Adversity"., 1962 December 2-3. (Box 16, Folder 21)
    Noted "MS Pending" for the Student Health Journal.
  - Discussion of "Hallucinations" paper., 1964 February 11-27. (Box 16, Folder 22)
    Noted "Pending," American Psychopathological Association, February 28, 1964.
  - "Hallucinatory Experiences"., 1963 December 10. (Box 16, Folder 23)
    Talk given to the American Psychopathological Association in February 1962, to be in Psychopathology of Perception.
  - "Misery Incorporated"., undated. (Box 17, Folder 1)
    LJW fiction, handwritten.
  - "On Losing Bill Blowitz"., 1964 August 18-1966 July 20. (Box 17, Folder 2)
    Submitted for publication to Poetry August 18, 1964. Revised version submitted to New Yorker Magazine July 20, 1966.
  - "The Hallucinogens"., 1966 February 8-1967 January 16. (Box 17, Folder 3)
    Book chapter for "Comprehensive Textbook of Psychiatry," Williams & Wilkins Co.
  - Voices: The Art and Science of Psychotherapy., 1967-1968. (Box 17, Folder 4)
    Noted "MS Pending."
  - "On Racial Violence"., 1965 March 26-June 21. (Box 17, Folder 5)
    Paper presented at the Henry Waldo Coe Foundation, Portland, Oregon March 26, 1965 and submitted for publication to Northwest United.
  - "Three Rebellions: Red, Black, and Green"., 1967 July 13-1968 January 15. (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - "Color of Tears"., 1962 March 24. (Box 17, Folder 7)
    Includes outline for "Black is the Stranger"
  - Untitled manuscript., undated. (Box 17, Folder 8)
    Manuscript about the "New Left"?
  - "Behavioral Sciences in the Medical School: A Progress Report"., 1965 May 26-November 2. (Box 17, Folder 9)
    LJW and Oscar A. Parsons
  - "Sleep Deprivation, Eye Closing and Microsleep"., 1965 June. (Box 17, Folder 10)
    "Liberson paper, "joint authorship with LJW, noted "pending."
  - "Hypnosis"., 1960, 1963, 1965. (Box 17, Folder 11)
    "In Consultation" article for Medical Tribune, noted "pending."
  - "Sleep: Questions and Answers"., 1965 July 19-1966 August 26. (Box 17, Folder 12)
    Prepared for the Journal of the American Medical Association, August 26, 1966. Noted "Publication Pending"
  - "A Discussion of Gorney's Theory of 'Shallow Water Euphoria' in SCUBA Divers"., 1966 January 4-May 16. (Box 17, Folder 13)
    Review for The Psychoanalytic Forum.
  - "1984"., 1966 August 28-1967 July 7. (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - "Impact of Information Theory Upon Psychiatry"., 1966 August 19-1967 September. (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - "Hallucinogens" and "Dissociative Reactions" (Folder 1 of 3)., 1965 January 26-1966 May 24. (Box 17, Folder 16)
    Prepared for the "Comprehensive Textbook of Psychiatry." Prepared for Williams & Wilkins Co. "Due August 1, 1965"
  - "Hallucinogens" and "Dissociative Reactions" (Folder 2 of 3)., 1965 February 4-1966 February 9. (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - "Hallucinogens" and "Dissociative Reactions" (Folder 3 of 3)., undated. (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - "The Othello Syndrome"., 1950, 1952, 1955, 1959, 1961, 1966-1967. (Box 18, Folder 3)
    Read at the 123rd Annual Meeting of the American Psychiatric Association in Detroit, MI.
  - Correspondence regarding LJW's writing., 1998 February 16. (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Reprints of LJW's articles., 1962, 1966-1969, 1971, 1973. (Box 18, Folder 5)
- 3. Office files., 1948-1998.
  The Office Files series contains three subseries: LJW in the Media; Consultation; Correspondence.
  - 3.1 LJW in the Media., 1955-1993.
    The LJW in the Media subseries contains clippings of newspaper and magazine articles about LJW or in which LJW was interviewed, as well as messages and correspondence from the media requesting interviews.
    - Newspaper and magazine clippings (Folder 1 of 2)., 1955 June-1969 July. (Box 19, Folder 1)
      Folder contains news articles about LJW or for which LJW was interviewed.
    - Newspaper and magazine clippings (Folder 2 of 2)., 1964-1965, 1968-1969. (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Newspaper and newsletter clippings (Folder 1 of 2)., 1981 November 9-1987 June 4. (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Newspaper and newsletter clippings (Folder 2 of 2)., undated. (Box 19, Folder 4)
      Folder contains news articles about LJW or for which LJW was interviewed. Clippings likely from 1965-1968
    - Newspaper clippings, newsletters, and related correspondence (Folder 1 of 2)., 1990 January-1993 August. (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Newspaper clippings, newsletters, and related correspondence (Folder 2 of 2)., 1980 May 27-1989 November 15. (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Newspaper and magazine clippings, interview transcript, and related correspondence., 1974 May-1979 May. (Box 19, Folder 7)
      Folder contains L.A. Times Magazine article "Kathryn and Louis West: Explorers of the mind, their fulltime project is to piece together puzzles of human behavior," March 16, 1975. Folder also contains "Psychology of cults" KNBC News conference transcript, December 1978.
    - Media contacts (Folder 1 of 3)., 1970 October 30-1987 February 27. (Box 19, Folder 8)
      Folder contains phone messages regarding LJW's interviews with various media organizations (newspapers, television), 5 envelopes.
    - Media contacts (Folder 2 of 3)., 1970 October 30-1987 February 27. (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Media contacts (Folder 3 of 3)., 1970 October 30-1987 February 27. (Box 20, Folder 2)
      Folder contains correspondence, itineraries, and phone messages regarding LJW's interviews with various media organizations (newspapers, television).
    - Summary of interviews., 1982 August 23-1987 June 24. (Box 20, Folder 3)
      Folder contains correspondence related to news interviews as well as a list of media appearances from 1975-1981 by topic.
    - Capital punishment., 1972 January 21- March 29. (Box 20, Folder 4)
      KCET taping of discussion on capital punishment, April 25, 1972.
  - 3.2 Consultation., 1956-1998.
    The Consultation subseries contains materials related to court cases in which LJW was asked to consult or serve as an expert witness.
    - West v. Barash, et al.., 1988 June 16- 1992 July 9. (Box 20, Folder 5)
      Correspondence regarding legal settlement. See Hart vs. McCormack and Center for Feeling Therapy.
    - Hart v. West (Folder 1 of 2)., 1986 September 22- 1989 July 7. (Box 20, Folder 6)
      See Hart v. McCormack and Center for Feeling Therapy
    - Hart v. West (Folder 2 of 2)., 1985 May 7- 1986 December 11. (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Edmondson v. Hill's Van Service., 1997 July- December 1. (Box 20, Folder 8)
      Folder contains correspondence and investigation report related to traffic accident legal case for which LJW consulted.
    - Phoenix House Foundation, Inc.., 1991 February 5-11. (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Dennis Schuck, Glendale City Attorney., 1991 February 7- October 15. (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Brian Wilson., 1994 January 26- March 16. (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Deposition Hart v. Cult Awareness Network (CAN) (Folder 1 of 3)., 1992 April 16-June 3. (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Deposition Hart v. Cult Awareness Network (CAN) (Folder 2 of 3)., 1992 June 3. (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Deposition Hart v. Cult Awareness Network (CAN) (Folder 3 of 3)., 1989 November 15- 1992 May 14. (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - 3.3 Correspondence., 1948-1994.
    The Correspondence subseries contains letters to and from LJW, primarily of a professional nature.
    - Correspondence., 1951 August 30-1956 March 27. (Box 21, Folder 3)
      Contains correspondence related to personal and professional matters including academic appointment at the University of Oklahoma. Also contains personal references and letters of recommendation regarding colleagues.
    - Correspondence., 1948 January 14-1955 October 22. (Box 21, Folder 4)
      Contains correspondence related to personal and professional matters. Also contains personal references and letters of recommendation regarding colleagues. Contains biography from 1955 for life insurance purposes.
    - Correspondence., 1960 April 15-1964 December 4. (Box 21, Folder 5)
      Contains correspondence related to personal and professional matters. Also contains personal references and letters of recommendation regarding colleagues.
    - Correspondence from colleagues with "A" last names., 1959 March 26-October 1, 1968 September 27-October 14. (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence from colleagues with "B" last names (Folder 1 of 2)., 1959 June 25-1961 January 3, 1965 April 13-1969 November 20. (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence from colleagues with "B" last names (Folder 2 of 2)., 1959 June 25-1966 April 6, 1969 August 27-September 23. (Box 21, Folder 8)
      Includes correspondence with Bruno Bettelheim regarding a visiting professorship by Bettelheim at the University of Oklahoma.
    - Correspondence from colleagues with "C" last names., 1970 May 13-1972 February 4. (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence from colleagues with "E" last names (Folder 1 of 2)., 1958 June 13-1961 August 1. (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence from colleagues with "E" last names (Folder 2 of 2)., 1955 May 16-1958 December 27. (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence from colleagues with "L" last names (Folder 1 of 4)., 1959 March 2-1969 December 17. (Box 22, Folder 1)
      Not in alphabetical order. May be correspondence with the same individual in all four files.
    - Correspondence from colleagues with "L" last names (Folder 2 of 4)., 1967 August 1-1971 June 22. (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence from colleagues with "L" last names (Folder 3 of 4)., 1959 October 27 -1967 December 4. (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence from colleagues with "L" last names (Folder 4 of 4)., 1957 December 2-1962 January 14. (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence from colleagues with "M" last names (Folder 1 of 4)., 1967 December 14-1969 December 9. (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence from colleagues with "M" last names (Folder 2 of 4)., 1965 February 26-1967 June 27. (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence from colleagues with "M" last names (Folder 3 of 4)., 1962 April 24-1964 November 10. (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence from colleagues with "M" last names (Folder 4 of 4)., 1958 August 12-1962 January 20. (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence from colleagues with "A" through "R" last names., 1987 April 10-1988 June 28. (Box 23, Folder 2)
      Folder contains correspondence from 1987-1988 with individuals with names beginning with "A" through "R". Primarily letters from LJW.
    - Correspondence from colleagues with "S" through "Z" last names., 1987 April 10-1988 June 28. (Box 23, Folder 3)
      Folder contains correspondence from 1987-1988 primarily with individuals with names beginning with "S" through "Z".
    - Correspondence (Folder 1 of 3)., 1988 June 24-1989 October 24. (Box 23, Folder 4)
      Folder contains correspondence from 1988-1989. Information redacted from letters before they arrived at University Archives and YRL Special Collections.
    - Correspondence (Folder 2 of 3)., 1987 August 4-1989 November 28. (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence (Folder 3 of 3)., 1987 July 3-1988 July 27. (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence with colleagues with last names "A" through "G"., 1990 January 2-June 27. (Box 23, Folder 7)
      Folder contains correspondence from January through June, 1990 with persons with the last names beginning with "A" through "G".
    - Correspondence with colleagues with last names "H" through "S"., 1990 January 4-June 28. (Box 24, Folder 1)
      Folder contains correspondence from January through June, 1990 with persons with the last names beginning with "H" through "S".
    - Correspondence with colleagues with last names "S" through "Z"., 1990 January 5-June 18. (Box 24, Folder 2)
      Folder contains correspondence from January through June, 1990 with persons with the last names beginning with "S" through "Z".
    - Correspondence with colleagues with last names "A" through "I"., 1990 July 20-1991 July 23. (Box 24, Folder 3)
      Folder contains correspondence from July 1990-July 1991 with persons with the last names beginning with "A" through "I".
    - Correspondence with colleagues with last names "J" through "T"., 1990 July 3-1991 June 28. (Box 24, Folder 4)
      Folder contains correspondence from July 1990-July 1991 with persons with the last names beginning with "J" through "T".
    - Correspondence with colleagues with last names "U" through "Z"., 1990 July 16-1991 May 28. (Box 24, Folder 5)
      Folder contains correspondence from July 1990-July 1991 with persons with the last names beginning with "U" through "Z".
    - Correspondence with colleagues with last names "A" through "K"., 1991 July 5-1992 June 25. (Box 24, Folder 6)
      Folder contains correspondence from July 1991-July 1992 with persons with the last names beginning with "A" through "K".
    - Correspondence with colleagues with last names "L" through "P"., 1991 July 10-1992 July 1. (Box 24, Folder 7)
      Folder contains correspondence from July 1991-July 1992 with persons with the last names beginning with "L" through "P".
    - Correspondence with colleagues with last names "R" through "Z"., 1991 July 9-1992 July 7. (Box 24, Folder 8)
      Folder contains correspondence from July 1991-July 1992 with persons with the last names beginning with "R" through "Z".
    - Correspondence with colleagues with last names "A" through "K"., 1992 July 20-1994 July 29. (Box 25, Folder 1)
      Folder contains correspondence from July 1992-July 1994 with persons with the last names beginning with "A" through "K".
    - Correspondence with colleagues with last names "L" through "R"., 1992 July 10-1994 June 29. (Box 25, Folder 2)
      Folder contains correspondence from July 1992-July 1994 with persons with the last names beginning with "L" through "R".
    - Correspondence with colleagues with last names "S" through "Z"., 1992 July 2-1994 June 28. (Box 25, Folder 3)
      Folder contains correspondence from July 1992-July 1994 with persons with the last names beginning with "S" through "Z".
    - Correspondence., 1969 April 29-1971 July 21, 1974 June 20. (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence., 1953-1956. (Box 25, Folder 5)
      Includes correspondence regarding University of Oklahoma School of Medicine
    - Williams & Wilkins Company., 1959 March 3-1960 April 11. (Box 25, Folder 6)
      LJW's correspondence with the publishing company.
    - American Jewish Archives., 1991 August 21-October 15. (Box 25, Folder 7)
      Correspondence pertaining to the Archives obtaining a collection on LJW's life and achievements.
    - Gibbons, Sheila., 1969 January 14-1970 December 11. (Box 25, Folder 8)
      Memos.
    - Rene Guyon Society., 1980 May 23-1986 September 29. (Box 25, Folder 9)
      Correspondence with and related to the Rene Guyon Society and Tim O'Hara.
    - Edelson, Marshall, M.D.., 1961 September 11-1963 August 8. (Box 25, Folder 10)
      Departmental correspondence with Marshall Edelson.
    - Sandoz Pharmaceuticals., 1959 February 10-1961 January 18. (Box 26, Folder 1)
      LJW's correspondence with the pharmaceutical company.
    - Knight, Robert P., M.D.., 1961 June 8-1963 May 20, 1966 May 18. (Box 26, Folder 2)
      Correspondence with Dr. Knight.
    - Goldstone, Sanford, Ph.D.., 1958 September 16-1959 January 26. (Box 26, Folder 3)
      Correspondence with Sanford Goldstone.
    - Galvin, John J.., 1961 January 24. (Box 26, Folder 4)
      Correspondence with John Galvin.
    - Farber, I.E., Ph.D.., 1956 April 24-1958 August 18. (Box 26, Folder 5)
      Correspondence with I.E. Farber.
    - Westinghouse-N.A.S.A. Conference., 1963 February 8-20. (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Payne, Hugh., 1960 January 19-1964 June 1. (Box 26, Folder 7)
      Includes "Eulogy for Hugh Payne" by LJW and "A Tribute To Hugh G. Payne, Sr.--Annex LF MF WK letters from more friends who know 'Who's Hugh'" June 7, 1963.
    - Bruch, Hilde (1 of 2)., 1961 July-1964 April 9. (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Bruch, Hilde (2 of 2)., 1960 January 30-1962 May 10. (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Johnson, Lyndon B.., 1966 August 22. (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - United States Air Force--Working group on survival training., 1955 December 14-1956 February 7. (Box 26, Folder 11)
      Correspondence related to USAF working group on how to most effectively train Air Force personal to resist enemy demands in case of capture. Includes letter from to B.F. Skinner (February 1, 1956)
- 4. Personal., 1948-1990.